nicheprofitclassroom.com 2019-01-09

# Privacy Policy

###  Niche Profit Classroom Privacy Policy

Niche Profit Classroom values Your trust. In order to honor that trust, all of Niche Profit Classroom's employee-owners are required to adhere to the highest ethical standards in gathering, using, and safeguarding any information You provide. Personal Information is gathered only when Users make voluntarily online submissions of such information or voluntarily establish an account.

**Collection of Your Personal Information**

Niche Profit Classroom collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Niche Profit Classroom also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Niche Profit Classroom. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Niche Profit Classroom for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Niche Profit Classroom Web site.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Niche Profit Classroom members-only message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Niche Profit Classroom does not read any of your private online communications. User is solely responsible for providing the equipment related to Accessing the Site, including all computer, remote communications equipment, telephone or other equipment.

Niche Profit Classroom encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from the Niche Profit Classroom members-only message boards so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Niche Profit Classroom is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the Niche Profit Classroom and Niche Profit Classroom family of Web sites.

**Use of Your Personal Information**

Niche Profit Classroom collects and uses your personal information to operate the Niche Profit Classroom Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Niche Profit Classroom also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Niche Profit Classroom and its affiliates. Niche Profit Classroom may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. Niche Profit Classroom may also contact you from time to time via your email address to provide you with a variety of information, including weekly wrap ups, newsletters, bulletins and similar information.

Niche Profit Classroom does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Niche Profit Classroom may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Niche Profit Classroom may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Niche Profit Classroom, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Niche Profit Classroom does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

Niche Profit Classroom keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Niche Profit Classroom, in order to determine what Niche Profit Classroom services are the most popular. This data is used to help us improve our product offerings.

Niche Profit Classroom Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Niche Profit Classroom or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Niche Profit Classroom; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Niche Profit Classroom, or the public.

**Use of Cookies**

The Niche Profit Classroom Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Niche Profit Classroom pages, or register with Niche Profit Classroom site or services, a cookie helps Niche Profit Classroom to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Niche Profit Classroom Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Niche Profit Classroom features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Niche Profit Classroom services or Web sites you visit.

**Security of Your Personal Information**

Niche Profit Classroom secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Niche Profit Classroom secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Changes to This Statement**

Niche Profit Classroom will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Niche Profit Classroom encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Niche Profit Classroom is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**

Niche Profit Classroom welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Niche Profit Classroom has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Niche Profit Classroom at the following web page: [https://yellowbird.freshdesk.com](https://yellowbird.freshdesk.com/)

We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
